

Kollegievej 6, st., -104, 9000 Aalborg, Denmark (willing to move)

□ (+45) 29405039 | ☑ robinbjerring@gmail.com | 🏔 www.robinbjerring.com | 🛅 robinwoelkbjerring

Summary_

Empathetic IT Design graduate skilled in game design, level design, project management, agile development, user experience and leadership. Love solving problems and creating new and compelling experiences. Have made video and board games, created a network for blockchain enthusiasts, owned an online comic book store and been a presenter as well as music planner for a festival.

Skills_

Design Game design, Level design, Design document, Photoshop, Gamification, Rapid prototyping, Excel for game stat management

Management Leadership, Agile Project Management, SCRUM, Kanban, Trello, Conflict management.

Users User testing, UX, analysis of user data.

Tech Unreal Engine, Unity Engine, Sourcetree/Git, C# programming basics, system administration.

Languages Danish (Native), English (Professional capacity), Norwegian Bokmål (read/understand), Swedish (read/understand).

Work Experience _____

DADIU Aalborg, Denmark

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2018 LEAD GAME DESIGNER, INTERNSHIP

- Lead Game Designer on iOS and Android game developed in Unity. Did game and UX design.
- Lead technical production. Communicated and coordinated with 17 students.
- Created test builds for quality assurance/UX testers.
- · Grade: A (ECTS).

Farum Municipality Farum, Denmark

IT SUPPORT INTERN Jan. 2017 - Mar. 2017

- · Upgraded hardware of laptop and desktop pcs.
- Installed OS and software.
- Did off-site administration of printers.
- Was introduced to VMware server administration.

Gjensidige Copenhagen, Denmark

BOOKER OF MEETINGS

- · Did B2B and B2C contact.
- · Set up meetings with potential customers.

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2016

Honors & Awards

Winner, Nordic Game Jam - Board Game Track (Jury & Public Choice Awards) 2016

Copenhagen, DK

Article, Apple included DADIU game Night Painter game in Made in Denmark list

Apple, DK

Education

Aalborg University Aalborg, Denmark

M.Sc. IT IN INTERACTIVE DIGITAL MEDIA

Sep. 2017 - Jun. 2019

· It design, agile project management, concept development, digital narratology, game design, gamification, prototyping.

Aalborg University Aalborg, Denmark

B.A. IN COMMUNICATION & DIGITAL MEDIA

Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2015

Educated in communication, media production, communication strategy, aesthetics.

AUGUST 13, 2019 ROBIN WOELK BJERRING · RESUME

Extracurricular Activity

Aalborg University Aalborg, Denmark

VOLUNTEER GUEST LECTURER Oct. 2017

- · Did lectures on Bitcoin and blockchain technology for peers.
- Created workshop where students had to come up with possible use cases for blockchain.

Aalborg Blockchain Network

Aalborg, Denmark Nov. 2017 - PRESENT

FOUNDER

· Founder of network for blockchain enthusiasts.

· Have done talks on various applications for blockchain technology.

Freedom Festival Aalbora

VOLUNTEER MUSIC PLANNER & PRESENTER

Jun. 2018 - Sep. 2018

- Contacted all bands and planned the festival music program. Handled 12 bands over two days.
- · Was the presenter for the festival. Stood on the scene and bit everyone welcome and introduced every band throughout the days.

Game Jam Participation Aalborg, Denmark

GAME DESIGNER, PROJECT MANAGER, CODER

2016 - 2019

- One Hour Game Jam, July 2019 Had one hour to create and upload a game. Made a choose your own adventure game in Unity and C# about having a devil and angel on your shoulder, who advises you on what to do with crunching in a game jam.
- Nordic Game Jam 2016 Winner of board game track. Game about betting and deception. Did game design and testing. Presented the game at nomination ceremony.
- · Global Game Jam, 2016 Designed a co-op game with wizards battling monsters with rhythm based magic combos.

University Projects

When music and difficulty meet:

How music affects perception of a video game's difficulty

Aalborg

MASTER THESIS

Jun. 2019

- Flow theory, SAM tests, psychophysiological data and user interviews.
- · Analyses whether the presence of music affects the user's perception of a game's difficulty.
- · Grade ECTS: B

Computer Games at the National Academy of Digital Interactive Entertainment (DADIU)

Aalborg Dec. 2018

SEMESTER EXAM ASSIGNMENT

· Exam in my game design and leadership work at DADIU as well as analytical reflections on the semester.

· Grade ECTS: A

"Well Played" - A Winning Strategy for eSport as a Business Model

Aalborg Jun. 2018

SEMESTER PROJECT

- · Investigates how multiplayer games can elevate eSport as a business model. Analyses loot boxes, battle passes and more.
- · Grade ECTS: B

The Pursuit of Intelligent Computer Games

Aalborg

SEMESTER PROJECT

Dec. 2017

- · Discusses current and future applications for self-learning algorithms (machine learning / AI) in video games.
- · Grade ECTS: B